Thank you for watching!
Good evening, everyone.
Good evening.
This is Akanezora, who will be proceeding today. Please give me your best regards.
Yay!
Yes, I'm Yukaya Lie. This is Yukaya Lie.
This is the 181st episode of "Ugka no Yukatani de Fu-Shon-Showroom".
I'd like to deliver another edition with a subtitle.
We'll decide on the subtitle with the users right here,
I'm going to deliver a program related to asari (Japanese horseradish),
This is Uka's original rule.
So, let's take a look at today's subtitle,
Today's subtitle is about the tour that ended the other day,
I would like to make a subtitle that expresses my appreciation for your hard work.
I would love to hear your suggestions and comments on the subtitle.
Please comment.
Please do.
A review of the spring tour.
Yes, that's right.
Good evening.
He said he hadn't seen you in a while.
Thank you.
Really?
Thank you very much.
Congratulations on your impression!
High tour Otsukuringu
Otsukuringu?
Otsukuringu
Congratulations on your tour!
He said he's delivering his objections to the tour.
It means "good-bye.
It's hard to tell.
I think it's this one.
Thank you for the tour.
No, it's not.
No?
It means something different.
You want to see it in a ball?
You want to see this in a ball?
Yeah, yeah.
Isn't this nice? Tour launch bash?
Oh, yeah!
It's like a party.
Yes, it is. A flower dance.
Okay, let's do this.
Wait a minute. I'll write it down.
The tour launch party.
Oh! Sounds fun!
Well, here it is.
Tonnella's.
So now that we have a subtitle, I'd like to do the title call.
Se-no!
Uka no
Delightful and Anxious Soul Moon
Tour Launch Banquet
Yoo-hoo!
Yes, so good evening everyone. We
Uka here.
Please give us a warm welcome.
So, please introduce yourself first, Mar-chan.
Yes!
Yes, I'm Marie Tsuruzawa. Pleased to meet you.
I am Director Murahoshi. Nice to meet you.
Today, I am solo from a new corner. Please give me your regards.
So, thank you very much for watching the 181st YUKKARI NO YUKKARI DE MINNA SHOWROOM today.
Thank you very much.
So, I know it's early, but I would like to spread the word here.
In order for as many people as possible to see this distribution,
I'm going to tweet about it on YUUKKARI's Twitter now, so please tweet about it.
Please tweet about it.
Today,
What shall we do today?
The studio has a spring-like atmosphere,
There will be tablecloths, flowers, and flags,
There are tablecloths, flowers, and flags, so shall we make it pretty?
Let's make it pretty. What about comments?
What are your comments?
Flowers.
Can we take it?
Oh!
Okay, white, white, white.
Do you want me to say "cute" or something?
I usually say "cute".
Cute.
You think it's cute?
COWIN.
Cowerwin.
Well, let's go with cute, shall we?
Yes.
Then, when the comments come in,
These are earrings.
Mr. Kakkotsu.
It was in the comments.
Ah! He says they're cute.
Okay. Let's go then.
Is it weird?
It's not weird.
It's just a little bit weird.
Oh!
That's close.
Too close?
I'll take a picture.
Okay, let's go. Ready.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Okay, okay, thank you very much.
I'll be on Twitter today.
I don't think so.
Yes, it's here.
I'd like to have a free talk about some recent events.
First of all, yes.
Well, let's leave the tour talk for now. Let's put it aside. I'll put it aside for later, as we'll look back on it a lot.
On Wednesday, June 21.
First major lie, we are going to release our first major first single!
Yes, we performed our new song "Tail Window" for the first time at the live that day, and the next day, April 17, it was made available for pre-sale from 0:00 am.
What is this song about? Oh, it's on!
Well, let's hear it once, it's playing.
That's about all I have to say.
Oh!
Molly molly.
Alarms that fade fast
Chopping on the heel of a bone that's hard to spit out
This is hard to do.
It's hard to get the whole group to go.
It's hard to get all three of us to go.
Because there's two of us
One katatsatu sliding world situation
This is Ehime Lismore
Sun.
miscellaneous knowledge
2nd
in the matter
3rd
Lance O
to
Yes.
OH!
That's good.
This one is a cheering song for spring.
Yes.
For those who are starting a new life, this is a campaign.
I'm sure there are many people who are starting a new life,
This song is a spring cheer song for them.
Yes, it's a spring cheer song.Yes, I have a very good song.
It is a very good song.
Hey, do you have any favorite points, Ma-chan?
Do you have any favorite points, Ma-chan?
Little by little, little by little.
About 8 dates, you see Ma-chan in the live performance,
Depending on her mood, she sometimes winks and sometimes not,
I think that's what people should watch for.
That's what I want people to see.
I think it's the lyrics.
The lyrics.
There are so many lyrics.
From 1A, it's very beautiful,
It's very beautiful from 1A.
There are so many lyrics.
It's very beautiful from the first verse,
When I say "hard-to-wear shoes," I mean, you know, when you start a new life, you put on new leather shoes, or loafers, or whatever,
Or loafers, for example,
You can wear shoes that you are not used to, but you can walk in them and take one step at a time,
I think it's really nice to feel a sense of new life and spring in that way.
It's nice.
In the last chorus, there are many lyrics cheering the singer on to do his best,
But they are all pretty much wasted,
The lyrics are the simplest and the most touching,
I hope you will listen to it.
It just takes a minute.
Let's listen to it.
The path we chose was a little different,
I'll always be on your side.
Hang in there, hang in there, hang in there.
When I get lonely, I'll come back to you.
Let's talk again.
Tell me your story.
It's good.
I know it is.
Please everyone, please subscribe and listen to it a lot.
Please listen to it a lot.
The dancing is cool, too, so I hope you will pay attention to it at the live performance.
Yes, that's right.
I'm sure you'll enjoy it,
Well?
Well, well..,
We have a lot of first single releases.
Here it is.
It's a little early,
We also have rock music.
The first day is this way.
It starts on April 29th,
30th, May 8th, and 5th,
The 5th is different.
There will be 6th and 7th.
So you will have a lot of opportunities to see a lot of dances.
Yes, you will have a lot of opportunities to see many dances.
See you later.
Yes.
And yes, there was a lot of live performance on that day,
New visuals have been released.
Let's take a look at the new visual.
Yes, it looks good from the top.
You can see it from the top.
This is the group's arsha.
This time the outfit is white,
There's a lot of extra room in the skirt,
It's very beautiful when it goes around.
That's one of the points,
The sleeves are 222,
The sleeves are 222, and there are two types of sleeves: hansari sleeves and stewel sleeves,
And also, the design of the skirt,
You're pushing it on.
There is a white design on the left side,
The proportion of the white design on the left side is totally different.
Yes, that's right.
The director, Ruri, and Rina have different 222 designs,
The three of us are different,
The three of us are different from each other, and Ayame and I are different from each other,
I think that is also a highlight,
The blue background with clouds floating on it also gives the impression of a new life,
It's nice, isn't it? It's spring.
This is also beautiful.
Is there a solo in this song?
Solo, too.
Next, please.
It's me.
He's laughing.
I learned this from a fan,
I was told by a fan that it's very rare to see a person smiling with his mouth open,
Like Asa.
That's for sure.
A lot of people tell me that this is their favorite,
It's new.
And it's the first time I've worn a half up-do,
I haven't really changed what I'm wearing for a long time,
It's my first time to wear a half updo.
It's kind of, you know, mature.
It's nice, isn't it? It's nice.
But you know what?
I'm 20 years old.
That's why?
I'm 20.
Really?
Yes. That's why.
But your face has changed, too. Yes, I guess so.
A little bit.
If I say a little.
I've always dreamed of a face that never changes, but I think it's changed a little bit.
You look cool.
Yes, it is. Next, please.
Oh, that's you, Moa-chan.
That's me.
Moa Shin's.
Sorry about the bangs. I can't lift my bangs.
You're lifting your bangs.
What do you call this haircut?
The parting?
The way it's parted.
Is this your first time?
It's fresh.
I thought it looked good on you.
It looks good on you.
It's really nice.
You've grown up. I knew it.
I was an adult.
I'm 17 years old.
By the way, maybe my hands are backwards.
Reverse.
Don't shake me. Don't shake it.
It's mature. That's nice.
Next then.
Okay.
Mr. Riju.
I'm Mr. Riju.
You are Mr. Riju, right?
Yes, that's right. I have not changed my grating. The last time.
I've talked about the last time and the previous times.
But I used to wear my hair straight, but now it's a little curly.
It's a little curly. This one, too.
Yes, a little. A little bit. Just lightly.
You are 20 years old, right?
Yes, because I'm 20.
That's nice.
It's good.
And your expression has become softer. Very much.
Yes, it did. I've been told that a lot. She has a softer look.
She has a goddess-like look.
Yes.Yes.
Isn't it?
I'm 20 years old.
Thank you very much.
You have three?
Then, please do.
Rimi-san.
Distance group.
Isn't that unusual? I don't know how to say it. I don't know, the angle.
The angle is right.
I thought it was quite unusual. It's the first time I've seen it.
But this hairstyle really suits you.
It looks good on her.
I don't think she's a princess, but I like the way she looks like a lady.
I like the way her hair flows. Pretty much here.
It's nice.
The feeling here.
Oh, the tips of the hair.
I like the tips of the hair.
It's snowing.
Nice.
Next, please.
Oh, you're Kawashi-chan, aren't you?
Are you a pony pail type, Ayame?
Yes, I am.
It looks like you've darkened your hair.
You said that.
The pony looks good on you.
Ayame also kind of likes it a lot when you open your mouth and smile.
Really? It's rare.
Indeed.
You can tell when you look at her properly, can't you?
It's unusual.
I can see that.
Next, please. Last.
It's Rina.
Oh, you must be Rina.
It's quite rare to see Rina's hair curly, isn't it?
That's unusual.
Is it curly?
Yes, it is.
It might be a little wavy. But...
The first time before, it was rather straight,
I think it was curly on the inside.
It's nice. It's kind of nice.
It looks good on you. It looks good on you.
But I don't see many people wearing white in casual wear, so it's refreshing.
That's for sure.
This is a common thing.
There are a lot of colors, too.
I think it's great that they are wearing costumes.
That's true. It's nice. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
This is how the new visuals have been released,
I look forward to working with you.
Please do.
Thank you very much. So, that's the end of this story for now,
Last Saturday and this Sunday, I performed in Taiwan LIVE,
On April 22nd, I performed at Idol Generation, and on April 23rd, I performed at Clawfest 2023.
Thank you very much.
We also had a live broadcast of the event,
Yes, that's right.
I hope some of you were able to see it.
What do you think?
I saw it, I saw it, I saw it.
The first Saturday of the month was Idol Generation's first live performance at Nakano Sun-plaza,
That's right.
Nakano Sun-plaza is closed.
So I think it was the last time we were going to perform,
I think the fans were the most happy.
They said they were glad to see us.
Nakano Sun-plaza is going to be closed and renewed.
It will be renovated in about 5 years.
They are planning to expand the capacity to 7,000 people.
That's what they said.
So I am glad I came.
It was the first time for me to go to a concert,
I had been to live shows before, but this was the first time for us to perform,
The view from the stage was really fresh and beautiful, wasn't it?
Yes, it was. It was amazing.
It was amazing to be standing on the stage.
But I was very happy that they could see my face standing there.
I thought it would make you happy.
What do you think?
The Sunplaza stage was huge.
It was really big.
It was huge.
But it was a lot of fun.
Because it was big and fun,
I felt like we could use the whole stage for dancing,
And there were many beautifully decorated sets,
There were monitors and so on,
The background matched our costumes,
I thought, "This background is really nice.
I admired it.
It felt good.
Let's fill the renovated Sun Plaza.
It's now Sunblasa.
Sun Plaza.
It's nice and spirited.
Yes, it is. I'll do my best for the renewed video again.
Thank you very much.
And you appeared in Chromes 2023, though,
How was it? How was it?
Oh, no.
It was really navy.
It was a little cold.
But, you know, we fought in Tokyo.
The three of us fought in Tokyo.
After the Tokyo battle, it got really warm when we left the concert.
It was pretty cold. Surprisingly.
We were on the side of the stage closest to the ocean,
I thought it was a great view of the ocean through the fans.
How did you interact with other idols? I mean, how did you interact with other idols?
What? Didn't you take a picture of my grandma?
Yes, she did. Dulli and I asked Fruit Zipper to take a picture of us together.
She was the cutest.
I have a purple girl named Noka Kudo, who is from Appanesan,
She is the same age as me and we are good friends,
So we met by chance,
We met in the elevator and decided to take a picture.
That's nice.
I guess that's how we interacted.
But it was Uka's first outdoor festival this year,
I don't know, but..,
It was a little cold before the show,
But when we were performing, it got hot,
But when we were performing, it became hot again, and I felt refreshed with the wind,
I was happy to be there,
It was a lot of fun.
Thank you very much.
Also, this was my first time at Kurofes,
If there is another one, please let me know.
Thank you very much.
So, thank you very much.
That's all for the free talk section.
Yay!
Now, let's get to today's project.
First of all, today's subtitle is "Tour Launch Banquet.
So, here is today's plan.
Tour Launch Banquet.
As it is?As it is?
A big feast.
Let's look back on the tour as if we were having a big feast.
First, let's decide on the venue.
Where is the grand banquet hall?
What do we do?
Is there anything in the grand ballroom?
What is it? The banquet hall?
Banquet hall.
What's that?
Have we ever had a banquet here?
Not yet.
Not yet?
Shabu-yaki.
Shabu-shabu?
Are you sure?
Is shabu-yaki okay?
We were just about to go there the other day.
I was really hungry on the way home from Nakano,
We were all talking about going to Shabuyo.
I see.
Then let's go to Shabuyo.
Shabuyo sounds good.
Pierce is.
You want to start from the entrance?
Can I sit down?
You mean, order a menu?
I'll order a menu.
Okay, as usual.
As usual.
Okay, bye.
Panel.
It's a panel.
Is that okay?
Yeah, it's fine.
You want a cow?
I'll have a cow.
Okay, let's have a cow.
Wouldn't it be too hard to finish with just pork?
I see.
Then let's have beef.
How about beef and chicken?
Chicken, cut it up a little bit?
A little bit?
Okay, that was important.
Okay, it's not chicken. Tsukune.
Tsukune.
Okay.
Here you go.
And tamanbo?
Dashi?
Oh, dashi.
You can't handle spicy food.
But lately I'm getting better at it.
Spicy and chige.
And sukiyaki?
Sukiyaki.
And one more.
One more.
Paitan?
Paitan OK.
Paitan, then.
Yes, it's done.
Okay.
Yes, you ordered.
Okay, drinks.
Okay, have a good day.
Order OK.
Okay.
What's that?
That's your first drink, right?
I'll have the first drink.
I'll have a cup of Urocha.
Uh, Uro-tea.
I'll have a Kurosucha.
Kuro-rocha.
Okay.
Then, I'm already at the shrine.
At the shrine.
Staff, here you go.
Is it me?
Yes, please.
Well, gentlemen, I'll take the opportunity,
What do you say? I'll bring it to you at a good time.
Good work, all three of you.
Thank you for your hard work.
Cheers.
Nice peach tea.
It's delicious.
Shall I do it?
What?
Hot pot.
It's okay. It's me.
Okay, then.
It's OK.
Ah, this way then.
Thank you. As usual.
Wait a minute. I have to post an insta-post saying thank you for today.
Oh, yeah.
All in one day, then.
Yes.
You're going to look back, right?
I have to think that it's okay to roll the camera now.
It doesn't have to.
I see.
Communication is about launching together.
Let everyone launch together.
What do you have?
What would you like to do?
I'd like to make a toast to the group.
I'm sorry. I thought the three of us would make a toast on our own.
Okay, everyone. Momochan, can you make a toast, too?
I think you had a good time at Uguka's live this time,
Let's have a toast.
Seino.
Cheers!
I would like to make a toast.
I did my best,
What was your favorite part? The most.
I had a great time at the dinner.
Dinner?
The meals were definitely fun in all the places we went.
Which meal was the most fun?
You mentioned a lot of places, you went to 6 cities, right?
Which one was it?
Thank you very much.
But still..,
Nagoya?
Yes. Nagoya, yes.
Are you okay, Sou-chan? Shall I let you in?
Let's go in. Let's do it.
It's good, isn't it? Nagoya was good, too,
I usually have takoyaki in Osaka,
Vegetables. Vegetables.
Thank you. Thank you.
But you went to eat kushikatsu.
I did. I did. In Osaka.
I thought the kushikatsu was delicious,
I didn't have many chances to go to kushikatsu. I never went to Kushikatsu.
I never did.
You can drink?
Excuse me.
One black licorice.
I'm sure I have some left.
I don't have any alcohol yet.
Then I'll have a glass of water.
Open? Open?Open? Open?
Oh, my God. Is everyone getting hungry?
Is it still okay?
No, I don't think so.
Can I have a couple of light shabu-shabu?
Okay, I'll do it.
Okay. Here you go.
Can I order edamame?
Mizuki ordered it too, so why not? Edamame.
Sure. Sure, sure.
You too, Mizuki.
With Mizuki.
Excuse me. Chopsticks. Chopsticks.
Chopsticks. Chopsticks.
It says "chopsticks. Chopsticks, please.
Can I have two points?
Four points.
Just in case.
I'm almost done.
Watch out. Watch out.
Mochisuki, give me some meat, Sora-chan.
Oh no.
How many more? How many more plates?
How many more plates?
Cow what?
Cow, cow what?
And..,
Five.
Cow five.
Curry, please.
I think I'll find some curry in the bathroom.
That's my curry.
You want some curry?
I'll have some.
Who wants waffles?
I want waffles.
You're early.
You're early. Waffles. Eating them.
It's like a change of pace.
Sora said it's a small plate.
Wait, sorry, sorry.
I want to put it in.
You're going to do it, Sora?
We're in.
Let's go.
Squeeze.
Ah, squeezing. Thank you very much.
We're in the middle of nowhere, so I'll just ask the waiter for a moment.
I'm sorry, clerk.
Shall I do it? Clerk.
Turn around.
Let's see...
What happened?
And why don't we talk about the set list?
Yes, I think so.
The setlist, you know.
We decided it ourselves, didn't we?
And you know, there were songs that we decided to play on this particular day, and there were songs that were fixed songs.
What does it mean to have fixed songs?
Wouldn't it be nice if we could try out a song that we felt comfortable with?
Yes, that's right.
The unusual one is "I can't go home".
Fixed level, right?
Fixed level.
Not a fixed class.
Fixed-graduated.
Fixed level is what they said about salary.
That's what this tour is about, the structure?
We talked about what we were going to do,
A tale of youth.
It's pretty much all there is to it.
Is it okay?
A coming-of-age story?
No, it was a coming-of-age story.
So I thought, "Why not start with Afternoon? That's what I was thinking.
That's right.
That's pretty much what we all agreed on.
Also, what about a coming-of-age song?
The first song that came up was "I Can't Go Home.
That's right.
We agreed that the song "Can't Go Home" should be fixed, since it is a part of the song that refers to youth,
It was very exciting, wasn't it?
That's right.
And the rest,
And then..,
Up.
But you were also particular about the order in which you put the songs in.
I really wanted to put them in the order in which they were recorded,
I wanted to do that, but..,
But that's enough.
I'm glad we were able to shout about our youth.
It was fun, wasn't it? You know...
It was quite rare.
Yes, it was.
I can't go back to my loafers. I'm glad.
And, hey, the loafers matched, too, right?
That's right. Loafers.
Yes, they are.
Loafers.
And the 8th song, Lies and Lilacs, I guess you could call it buying.
I'm eating.
They're eating.
They're eating. They're eating.
It was a replacement,
I also have lies and lilacs,
What do you call it? It's a romantic song,
I think it has a little bit of sadness of youth,
A sense of youth.
That's pretty good.
That's why. So, I did include it.
Yes, I did.
Also, it depended on the show,
For the regional shows, the lead back was always included,
But for the Yokohama and Tokyo shows, you were particular about the position of the lead backdrop under the hamiluri.
That's right.
Also, we didn't make an encore brook this time,
I see.
I didn't dare to make an encore,
And then, we added "Kototirab" and so on,
Kotochilab" is a program in which fans introduce local delicacies and specialties of the area to the audience,
It is a radio project in which fans introduce local delicacies and local specialties, and Ruri and I introduce them on stage,
That's right.
It was a radio program called "Yukari Mesume no Yukari Dia" (Yukari Mesume's Yukari Dia),
I think it was a good idea to do that on stage,
How was it? How did you like it?
How was it?
Did you hear of anyone who used it?
I have the image that it was quite lively.
Yes, it was.
There was a lot of laughter.
Kototillabu,
It was a good project, doing all kinds of things.
We were also invited to Kototirabu.
Afterwards, and so on.
It was fun.
I thought I heard a bouncing sound.
And at the last show at the Cinastera Ball, we made a block for encores,
I dared to make a block for encores,
Yes, that's right.
I asked everyone to do it, and we did an encore encore,
We performed a new song, "Tail Window",
This was also the first time for you to hear an encore, wasn't it?
Yes, it was.
It was the first time for me to hear an encore, wasn't it?Because it involved shouting from inside the ship.
But we always do encores, but this time we decided not to do them,
I'm not the same as those who say they haven't heard it,
I'm not the same as those who said they didn't hear it,
I had to go back to Cosmic School to prepare for the benefit concert,
So, I think the first time I heard the encore was at the Stellar Ball,
I think the first time I heard an encore was at the Stellar Ball.
So I think the last day at Stellar Ball was a memorable one for both of us.
Yes, it was.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
It's nice.
Also, Cosmic was a special version of the Stellar Ball.
Yes, it was.
And that one, has anyone ever done that before?
That was actually decided at the rehearsal.
At today's rehearsal.
We were going to dance as usual,
But the Stellar Ball is big, and it's wide horizontally,
I was told by the staff that I could use it more.
So we were on stage thinking what to do,
Then, we talked about how we were going to have fun together without pretending to dance,
And we ended up deciding on this one.
How was it?
No one made a mistake, right?
I made a mistake.
What do you think?
I'm saying, "Oh, yeah.
Yes, actually.
That's right.
After all, he said, "Hey, hey, hey, ai ai ai" to everyone there,
I'm glad.
Sada-chan, you're shaking your head.
This is it.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry.
I beg your pardon.
Sada, everyone there is still shaking a lot.
If I tell you to eat, it's OK.
Excuse me.
Face.
Thank you.
Speak quickly.
That's right. Leary's combination was good,
Yes, it was.
I've been enjoying Cosmic's work more and more.
That's true.
I think that since the previous generation's performance, people were wondering how to paint Cosmic at first. Everyone was.
But from then on, it was fine,
I don't know, it's just...,
Sad.
The chorus of calls, I guess everyone was getting used to it.
I guess we also encouraged the audience at the end in Shinagawa, and it was a great turnout.
It was fun.
Do you have any memorable moments?
Certainly.
It was a lot of pressure on the chest. It's been a long time since I've called a concert, so it was a lot of fun.
That was the call, wasn't it? I wonder, in a coming-of-age story, you can see where the call will come in. I can see where the call is going to come in.
I'm sure that's true. Thanks. It was something to look forward to, wasn't it?
Yes, it was. It was a sense of togetherness.
Is there anyone at the end?
Oh, I've done it before. What?
What? What?
I delivered the cat.
It's arrived!
I delivered the cat!
Thank you very much.
I got your girl!
Thank you very much!
She's a good talker.
I got it!
You're so funny.
You suddenly did something funny.
There she is.
That kitty was here, wasn't she?
That's right.
I'm sorry. We're waiting for you.
It looks a little like him.
Yes!
It's not a resemblance.
Yes, it is.
The ribara turned out to be an outrageous side piece.
That was fun.
It sure was. I could tell a lot from the stage.
I like the flow from Coriolis to Girls' Night.
You might get it. I can understand the Weste show.
Oh, I see.
We learn it by the connection. We do.
That's right.
I wonder what the next song is.
But it's nice. It's a cool block.
I'm glad you all enjoyed it.
I'm actually eating this by now, so it's not nearly there,
Are you all full?
Yes, I am.
Is there anyone who hasn't eaten yet?
I'm scared.
Next.
Dessert?
Maybe some vanilla ice cream to cleanse the palate.
Vanilla.
Buff, buff, buff, buff, buff, buff.
Thank you.
Would you like me to get you some vanilla?
Would you like some vanilla?
I want some more vanilla.
I want some more vanilla. I'm off then.
I brought vanilla ice cream.
There you go.
Then, let's do this to Rizuna.
Thank you very much.
Yes, I'll do it like this.
Then, please have some for everyone.
After all, I want to eat vanilla ice cream and ice cream care.
I guess so.
Then, please eat it. Riz.
I put too much in.
It's delicious.
Come here.
It came out.
Watch out, watch out, watch out.
Watch out, watch out.
Delicious, delicious, delicious, delicious.
Did you finish eating?
I finished eating.
Yes, so, I'd like to say goodbye to the big performance,
It was fun, wasn't it?
Well then, Moa-chan, please close the show.
Yes, I will.
So, everyone.
Ipponjime?
Yes, let's go.
Let's go. Ready?
Wow.
What? Black Ulon.
Thank you very much.
It's about time.
You've prepared it.
The big performance is about to end.
I'm going to close at the end.I'm going to close at the end.
It's like an overtime game.
In overtime. Do you want in?
I'll put it in.
I'll do it.
If it's business as usual, it's me.
If it's the same as usual.
If it's the same as usual, it's me, right?
Then, I'll put it in.
Sora did it and told the story.
Sora did it.
I'm always Story's person.
Who's that Black Ulon guy?
Yes, that's me.
What's the difference between Black Ulon and Ulon-chan?
What's the difference?
I'm a Black Urchin because I'm strong at losing body fat and stuff.
I am also a Black Uronian.
I'm a black uron. I think so.
Thank you.
I feel that way.
So that's how it is. Well then.
So, as I recall, the black toys are more...
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
So since training is such a hassle, I'll put Yuka in until the last minute.
I see.
Then which one should I choose?
Eh, that, that's the famous water.
Bye bye.
That much? Was it that much?
You definitely prefer ginger ale, don't you, Sora?
That's right. Definitely.
If there is no melon soda, it's ginger ale.
So that's how it is.
Actually, I like melon soda the best.
Melon soda. It looks so good.
It's got a lot of temperature.
What would you like?
Snow and wind, then?
Yes, it is.
Thanks for the spring tour, Nya!
I've got something.
Thanks for the spring tour!
Let's keep working hard together!
So, let's have a good time!
Cheers!
Cheers! Cheers!
Cheers, everyone!
A real toast.
Yummy.
It's good.
I was going to say delicious. Yummy.
Yummy.
So that's how it is. What's with Black Dai-chan?
He's a strong guy at the shrine.
That's right. The color is kind of black.
What? Black mouth?
There is such a thing.
That's what I mean.
He's an adult.
Twenty. I'm 20.
Delicious.
Looks delicious.
Maybe she's good at dancing.
Really?
I'm 20.
You will need it from now on.
It's delicious.
It's delicious, Kurodai-chan.
I'd like to receive a big thank you from all of you for your hard work.
I would like to receive it.
Please do.
Octopus floating.
Golden octopus.
Thanks for your hard work.
Thank you.
Thank you, JETS!
Mirror ball.
Thanks for your hard work.
Good work.
Oh, you said it.
You did a great job on the tour.
Thank you very much.
It was really great that the six of us could do all the shows together.
It was great.
It went by so fast.
Thanks for your hard work. You guys are the best.
You guys are the best.
Good night. Ah, there are a lot of cats here. Thank you.
I'm glad we all made it through.
I'm glad. I'm really glad.
The tour started in late February and ended in April.
It was a lot of fun, and I have a lot of memories from the tour.
Thank you very much for your hard work. Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
I am glad to hear that you have commented on how much you have grown.
I am glad to hear that you have commented that you are growing.
Thank you very much.
Mr. Luckiyo. I was drinking from 3:30 p.m. today. Thank you for your hard work.
What time is it?
Even now, it's 7:00 p.m.
That's amazing.
That's too much. I envy you.
I'm jealous.
It's amazing.
Has the bond among the members deepened?
Yes, we did. We went bowling.
I think it's pretty important.
The bond among the members is getting stronger.
You like bowling too much, don't you?
You have changed.
The bond between the members has deepened, and I feel like I've become closer to the staff as well,
Throughout this tour, I've been thinking about how today's sound ball went, and how it was like,
We would talk about how today's sound ball went, how it went, how we should do it next time, and so on,
I think we grew in many areas, even in terms of technical skills.
Yes, it was.
Moa-chan, you got the highest score.
I got 67 points, but thank you very much.
It was the first time I participated in Uguka's one-man show. Masano Shinagawa.
Thank you very much.
I hope you will come and visit us again if you like.
I will be at Lady from this Saturday,
If you were in charge, you would be in Shinjuku.
That's right. That's right. By all means.
Please do.
Check.
Check, huh?
Okay, then,
It was delicious. Very good.
It was delicious.
Okay, bye-bye, everyone.
See you later.
You lied about everything.
So, please pay your bill, everyone.
Well, that's all for now, isn't it?
That's it, that was the grand performance for the launch of the tour.
So that's it,
Oh, this way.
Ei, kai.
That's it.
I'll pay you, Mr. Music Band!
Thank you!
It's not out. It's not out.
I'm sure.
I'm not out.
Thank you very much.
Ginga Guitar is at Pepe Barlai.Mr. Ginga Guitar is at Pepe Barlai.
Contemporary. Very interesting.
Everyone, please shut up.
Thank you very much.
So, we are ending the 180th Athem of Flash Orem with the Uka no Yuuka de Flash Orem.
Please.
It's not "please.
Thank you very much.
So, this is an announcement from Ukka.
Yes.
The release of the first major single will start this Saturday.
This Saturday, April 29th, it will be held at Shinjuku Maruimen Rooftop.
The next day, Sunday, there will be a live streaming and online signing event.
This will be at Space Emo.
That's right, he said that there are no additions, so be sure to get there early because that's all they are selling right now.
That's right.
I was really close.
I've already finished.
Please do it.
Please, everyone, please.
The next day, May 4, is the Golden Week festival at AEON MALL Tsunena.
The next day, May 5, is also in Aichi, and I will be performing at a festival in Taiwan.
JCIF's 2023.
Please come to this festival as well. Please come to this festival as well.
The next day, we will go to Osaka and perform at Hankyu Nishinomiya Gardens.
And finally, on May 7, I will be at the Edobashi Umeda Exhibition.
This is the schedule for Golden Week.
We are still looking forward to seeing you all in June and July. Please come to various places.
Nishinomiya. Fixation. Hankyu Nishinomiya Gardens.
Please come.
Next.
This way.
On May 21, there will be another edition of Kawaii Shines at Sanrio Puroland.
The performers will be Uka, Minoru Ogi, and Pochakko.
Yurikamo-Okimae and Rinmo-Okimae will be a double collaboration.
I'm so happy. We are able to perform at Sanrio Puroland again this year.
Lurie couldn't make it last year, so this time we would like to perform with six members.
Tickets will go on sale to the general public on Saturday, April 29 at 20:00.
Please come and join us. Please come.
Please come.
And, I'll be back soon,
This one is coming soon, too. It was a little further away.
On Saturday, June 3, at Studio Freedom in Shibuya, there will be Yukirin's solo live performance of Aoruri's birthday.
It's the first time.
Yukirin's Blue Ruri Birthday Solo Live at 10:00 a.m., followed by a What is?
The second part will be happy idol dee, cute but jam-packed live from 6:30pm.
The Oojyubugakusei?
Fficial advance registration is now being accepted.
It seems that the hearts after Ruri's "Great Traffic Jam" have disappeared on the site.
The heart is the point, so don't forget it.
I had a chance to see a little bit of the two of them, and it was great to see them as themselves, or more like the two of them.
It was great to see them.
They are totally different from each other.
I think it will be fun to see both parts of the show.
I hope you will all come. Please come.
And..,
Uka! I will be having a one-man live concert.
First, on Saturday, September 30 at Shibuya Wig, then on Saturday, October 14 at Tokyo Kinema Club, and finally on Sunday, January 21 at Liquid Room in Ebisu.
Please come and join us. Please come and join us.
That's all for now.
I would like to check the top 5 ranking first.
I would like to start with the top 5 ranking.
Fifth place, Ms. Rie Shibari. Thank you very much.
And, in fourth place, Ganryu Shimaotai-san. Thank you very much.
Third place, Enzu-san. Thank you very much.
And 2nd place, Ken-san. Thank you very much.
First place, Risaku. Thank you very much.
The next episode will be on Wednesday, May 10, at 7:00 p.m.
Please subscribe to our favorite programs by clicking the hat mark so that you don't miss any of them.
I will also be doing a private webcast, so please check it out.
So, there will be no review session this time.
I was just acting.
No acting eye, I just did it for sure.
So, that's it for today, the 181st edition of Ukka's Yukari Fenasho Room.
As I mentioned earlier, the next session will be on Wednesday, May 10 at 7:00 p.m. The members will change again, so please come and join us.
The members will change again, so please come back and watch the next one.
That's all for now.
Thank you very much.